esuhsd.org 2004-12-04

# Privacy Policy

**Personal Information:** | ESUHSD does not collect personal information about individuals without their knowledge. Personal information may be requested when you engage in any of the following online activities:   
  
* Use District Email.   
* Submit information to the site via a form. This includes activities such as completing a feedback form or an online application. 

|   
**Use of Personal Information** | We do not collect any personal information unless you voluntarily provide it by sending us e-mail, participating in a survey, or completing an on-line form. Personal information submitted will not be transferred to any non-affiliated third parties unless otherwise stated at the time of collection. When a user submits personally identifiable information it is used only for the purpose stated at the time of collection.For example, our Online Job Application is stored to provide you and our Human Resources Department access to the account. Any information collection on this Web site is only used for District purposes. |   
**Students:** | Parents have the right to approve, disapprove, or revoke a previously granted right to post a student's picture or other personally identifiable information.  |   
**E-mail:** | If you send us an electronic mail message (e-mail), the message will usually contain your return e-mail address. If you include personally identifying information in your e-mail because you want us to address issues specific to your situation, we may use that information in responding to your request. Remember that e-mail is not necessarily secure against interception. Please send only information necessary to help us process your request. If you send e-mail to us, it will be forwarded to those individuals (employees, school board members) necessary to address that e-mail. |   
**E-mail Lists:** | The information we collect when you subscribe to one of our e-mail lists is used solely to administer these lists and is not shared, disclosed or sold to other organizations. Users who no longer wish to receive our notifications may opt-out of receiving these communications.  |   
**Links to Other Sites:** | The ESUHSD web site provides links to other web sites. ESUHSD is not responsible for the privacy policies of other web sites, and ESUHSD'S privacy policy does not apply when you visit these other sites. We recommend that you be aware when you leave our web site and encourage you to read the privacy statements of other web sites you visit.  |   
**Anonymous Information and Log files:** | Our web site will automatically record some broad demographic information, such as a visitor's country, operating system, browser types, frequency of visit, and so on. This tracking system does not record information about individuals. We use this information for statistical analysis, to help us make our site more useful to visitors. The information is not reviewed on an individual basis but is aggregated with other users for comparison purposes. |   
**Cookies:** | A “cookie” is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. It enables ESUHSD to store and track what you are looking at when you visit the ESUHSD site. If you are concerned about the potential use of information gathered from your computer by “cookies,” you can set your browser to prompt you before it accepts a “cookie.” Most Internet browsers have settings that allow the identification or rejection of “cookies.” |   
**Security:** | ESUHSD takes reasonable precautions to protect your personal information. When you submit information via the web site, it is protected both online and off-line. When personal information is required, that information is stored in a secure file on our server. We also take precautions to protect user information off-line. All user information is restricted to authorized employees. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific task are granted access to personal information. The server used to store personal information is kept in a secure environment. |   
**Changes to this Privacy Policy:** | FUSD may amend this policy from time to time. FUSD will prominently display on this Web site any substantial change in the way we use your personal information. |   
**Contact Us:** | If you have questions about this privacy statement or the comments about the web site please email [webmaster@esuhsd.org](mailto:webmaster@esuhsd.org) or write to:

Webmaster  
East Side Union High School District  
830 N. Capitol Avenue  
San Jose, Ca 95133

|
